

### **Contact**

- □ rahulsaviour2804@gmail.com
- **\** 7979734249
- Pangalore, Karnataka

#### **Personal Details**

• Date of Birth : 28/04/1995

• Nationality: Indian

## **Skills**

SAP ABAP	80%
Hard working and quick learner	100%
RICEF objects	80%
S4HANA	60%

### **Achievement & Awards**

Rising star

### Language

- Hindi
- English

#### **Interests**

 Gym, Cricket, Badminton, chess, reading motivational books.

# **Objective**

Total 4.5 years and relevant to ABAP Consultant 3 years of SAP R/3 Material Management, Sales Document and Plant Maintenance module experience in version (ECC 6.0, ECC 4.6, ECC 7.3).

I have 2 full life cycle implementations and 2 post go-live support projects experience. Worked on ECC to HANA migration projects.

Interacted with Subject Matter Expert (SMEs), Business Process Owners(BPOs), Business champions, Project Management office to design Business Blueprints and formulate the fit-gap analysis.

ABAP experience includes designing technical specifications documents. Experienced and worked on RICEF concepts involving all types of reports ( Classical, ALV and Interactive ), Interfaces, Conversions, Enhancements, BADIs, BAPIs, RFCs, Function Modules, BDC and OData. Extensive experience in all phases of testing and debugging, from Integration, Unit, User acceptance and regression testing.

Proactively supported as functional supplier also to improve process quality, reduce and resolve open tickets and improve overall cycle time.

### **Experience**

CGI
 Senior Software Engineer
 SAP ABAP Consultant

31/08/2024-Present

- CGI( Parent Organisation 06/03/2024-30/08/2024
   Orcapod Consulting Pvt Ltd)
   SAP ABAP Consultant
   Working here as an SAP ABAP Consultant. Working in
   S4HANA migration projects.
- Diverse lynx India Pvt. Ltd 23/02/2024-05/03/2024
   Senior Software Engineer
   Working as an SAP ABAP Consultant.
- Innovapptive Global Solutions 24/01/2022-16/02/2024
  SAP ABAP Developer
  I have worked across multiple clients on PM and MM
  modules, where my job is to understand the client
  requirements and deliver the product needs accordingly.
  I have worked on BADIs, Function modules, Reports,
  RFCs, Enhacements,RICEF and other SAP objects. I am
  also involved in code review for performance tuning.
  I am well versed in troubleshooting and debugging.
  Supported projects business live issues after go-live.
  Completed 2 End To End Implementations.
- PA Projects Pvt Ltd 20/07/2019-20/02/2021
   Project Execution Engineer
   Worked as a project execution engineer where my role is
   for the erection and commissioning of a wide plate mill.

#### Education

- NM Institute Of Engineering And Technology 02/06/2019
   Mechanical Engineering
- Ramakrishna Mission English High School 10/04/2014
   Pure Science
- Sister Nivedita English High School 10/04/2012

  Pure Science

		•	
D	ra	$\sim$	~+c
_		_	cts
	$\cdot$	_	~~

# Client name - Airgas ltd

Project type - Implementation and go live support.

Project - Implementation of mInventory and mWorkorder mobile application on PM and MM module.

Role - SAP ABAP Consultant.

Responsibilities - to develop or implement the mobile application according to customer business needs.

Here I have also worked in S4 Hana migration.

### • Client Name - Rio Tinto Itd

Project type - implementation and go live support.

Project - Implementation of mInventory and mWorkorder mobile application on PM and MM module.

Role - SAP ABAP Consultant.

Responsibilities - to develop or implement the mobile application according to customer business needs.

Here I have also worked on S4 Hana migration.

### • Client Name - Bell

Project type - support

Role - SAP ABAP Consultant

Responsibilities - to support and solve the issues of users from different SAP modules like MM,SD and FI.

Rahul Kumar